UNITE Education Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/022 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ILGWU Memorable Media Moments in Labor History, 4 (Box 40)
- ILGWU - Susan, Judy and Jamin, Ramona -- 5/9/1991, 5 (Box 40)
- Ambulance Rallies - 10/8/1991, 6 (Box 40)
- Ambulance Rallies -- 10/8/1991 -- tape #2, 7 (Box 40)
- Ambulance Rallies -- 10/8/1991 -- tape #3, 8 (Box 40)
- Rainfair Strike - 10/5/1991, 9 (Box 40)
- Garment Workers -- July 19, 1991, 10 (Box 40)
- Child Labor -- tape #653, 1 (Box 41)
- Peddlers in NYC: Immigrant Labor -- tape #677, 2 (Box 41)
- Jay Mazur/Rain Fair -- tape #676, 3 (Box 41)
- Crafted With Pride Made in USA "Excuses" -- 9/10/1990, 4 (Box 41)
- The Bobbin Show Video -- tape #671, 5 (Box 41)
- Made in USA: Moving -- tape #670, 6 (Box 41)
- Jobs With Justice -- tape #717, 7 (Box 41)
- The Sexual Harassment Quiz -- tape #721, 8 (Box 41)
- A Modular Manufacturing Shop -- tape #720, 9 (Box 41)
- Fighting For Workplace Fairness -- tape #723, 10 (Box 41)
- Keeping The Promise: Social Security and Senator Patrick Moynihan -- 9/13/1988, 11 (Box 41)
- ILGWU -- tape #634, 12 (Box 41)
- Dinkins Speaking to ILGWU -- tape #632, 13 (Box 41)
- Child Labor Abuse -- tape #652, 14 (Box 41)
- Child Labor NYC -- tape #655, 15 (Box 41)
- ILGWU--David Dinkins -- tape #637, 16 (Box 41)
- ILGWU Labor Rally: Local 399 -- tape #631, 17 (Box 41)
- Working At Home Issue -- tape #630, 18 (Box 41)
- ACTWU In Action, 19 (Box 41)
- The Voucher Corporation -- 8/9/1989, 20 (Box 41)
- Segment on Child Labor -- tape #673, 21 (Box 41)
- Christmas At Starcross -- tape #708, 22 (Box 41)
- We Do the Work -- tape #706, 23 (Box 41)
- Health Care -- tape #778, 1 (Box 42)
- Hightower ACTWU Convention -- tape #833, 2 (Box 42)
- Watsonville On Strike -- tape #840, 3 (Box 42)
- The New Immigration Law -- tape #842, 4 (Box 42)
- Leslie Fay Settle -- tape #841, 5 (Box 42)
- Behind the Seams -- tape #759, 6 (Box 42)
- Mario Cuomo -- tape #763, 7 (Box 42)
- American -- tape #745, 8 (Box 42)
- ILGWU: NAFTA -- tape #772, 9 (Box 42)
- ILGWU/ATWU Merge -- tape #774, 10 (Box 42)
- ILGWU-NAFTA -- tape #770, 11 (Box 42)
- Campaign for Healthcare Reform -- tape #769, 12 (Box 42)
- CBS Sunday Morning -- tape #891, 13 (Box 42)
- Canada's National Health Program -- tape #892, 14 (Box 42)
- Stephan Chemical -- tape #846, 15 (Box 42)
- The Story of a Plant Closure -- tape #845, 16 (Box 42)
- The Story of a Plant Closure -- tape #845, 17 (Box 42)
- 1989 ILCA Award Winners -- tape #844, 17 (Box 42)
- Re: Health-Tex Problems -- tape #864, 18 (Box 42)
- The Dream Continues -- tape #861, 19 (Box 42)
- Hercules -- tape #860, 20 (Box 42)
- NAFTA -- tape #895, 21 (Box 42)
- Minimum Wages -- tape #897, 22 (Box 42)
- Arrow & Minimum Wage -- tape #896, 23 (Box 42)
- Leslie Fay/ILGWU Settle -- tape #881, 24 (Box 42)
- Special Assignment Report: Sweatshops in New York -- 11/30/1993, 25 (Box 42)
- Organizing Segment -- tape #914, 1 (Box 43)
- Organizing -- tape #918, 2 (Box 43)
- ACTWU Expose -- tape #917, 3 (Box 43)
- Standing Your Ground On Safety -- tape #900, 4 (Box 43)
- Look For the Union Label -- tape #898, 5 (Box 43)
- Labor Today Segment -- tape #899, 6 (Box 43)
- Mississippi Masala -- tape #933, 7 (Box 43)
- Common Frontiers -- tape #932, 8 (Box 43)
- CUNY Conversations -- tape #912, 9 (Box 43)
- Today Series on Labor -- tape #936, 10 (Box 43)
- A Need for Victory -- tape #935, 11 (Box 43)
- Triangle Fire & Misc. -- tape #894, 12 (Box 43)
- Innocence Lost: the Verdict -- July 21, 1993, 13 (Box 43)
- The High Road -- tape #908, 14 (Box 43)
- Union Hands -- tape #944, 15 (Box 43)
- American Dream -- tape #915, 16 (Box 43)
- Jack Sheinkman Interview -- tape #913, 17 (Box 43)
- California Working -- tape #843, 18 (Box 43)
- Cuomo-ACTWU Convention -- tape #834, 19 (Box 43)
- Conference on Trade & Competitiveness -- tape #847, 20 (Box 43)
- AVTEX -- tape #911, 21 (Box 43)
- Innocence Lost: the Verdict -- tape #910, 22 (Box 43)
- Leslie Fay: We Don't Buy It -- tape #741, 23 (Box 43)
- It's All About Jobs -- tape #756, 24 (Box 43)
- Taking Civil Rights to Heart -- tape #1068, 1 (Box 44)
- Labor Day -- tape #1066, 2 (Box 44)
- It's About Jobs -- tape #1059, 3 (Box 44)
- Closing of Hathaway Shirt Co. -- tape #1039, 4 (Box 44)
- Covering the Workplace, 5 (Box 44)
- Hathaway Worker & Hilary Clinton -- tape #1038, 6 (Box 44)
- Ties That Bind -- tape #1056, 7 (Box 44)
- Labor Beat -- tape #1051, 8 (Box 44)
- Rev. Jesse Jackson -- tape #1062, 9 (Box 44)
- Jim Hightower -- tape #1061, 10 (Box 44)
- Dateline -- tape #1040, 11 (Box 44)
- Immigration/Virginia Coughlin -- tape #1032, 12 (Box 44)
- Be Encouraged -- tape #1030, 13 (Box 44)
- Proposed Merger -- tape #1037, 14 (Box 44)
- High Price of Fashion -- tape #1034, 15 (Box 44)
- 1995 Convention -- tape #1033, 16 (Box 44)
- Picking Up the Torch -- tape #1029, 17 (Box 44)
- Katie Quan/UNITE -- tape #1027, 18 (Box 44)
- Ch.28 News -- tape #1025, 19 (Box 44)
- Immigrant Workers, 20 (Box 44)
- Larry King Live -- tape #1026, 21 (Box 44)
- Tools of the Trade, 22 (Box 44)
- Building Dreams & Transit Tech, 23 (Box 44)
- When Children Do the Work, 24 (Box 44)
- Lineman's Rodeo & 24hr Day Care, 25 (Box 44)
- Prison Labor -- tape #1119, 26 (Box 44)
- Union Workers -- tape #1124, 27 (Box 44)
- Building Peace in the Midst of War -- tape #1122, 28 (Box 44)
- Downsizing -- tape #1112, 29 (Box 44)
- Stop Sweatshops Campaign - tape #1096, 1 (Box 45)
- Make It Happen -- tape #1100, 2 (Box 45)
- Celebrity Scandals -- tape #1125, 3 (Box 45)
- Inside Look At Collective Bargaining -- tape #1099, 4 (Box 45)
- UNITE Sweatshop Protest -- tape #1097, 5 (Box 45)
- Looking Back: Moments in Labor History, 6 (Box 45)
- What Happened to the Amer. Dream -- tape #1088, 7 (Box 45)
- Rain Fair Story -- tape #1094, 8 (Box 45)
- UNITE '95 Merger -- tape #1101, 9 (Box 45)
- Workplace Profiles, 10 (Box 45)
- Leslie Fay Rally - tape #1118, 11 (Box 45)
- UNITE Sweatshop Rally -- tape #1149, 12 (Box 45)
- Slave Labor/ILGWU -- tape #1128, 13 (Box 45)
- Reports on Sweatshops -- tape #1127, 14 (Box 45)
- Labor & Economy -- tape #1113, 15 (Box 45)
- Made in New York -- tape #1117, 16 (Box 45)
- ACTWU Shorts -- tape #1154, 17 (Box 45)
- Protest At Famous-Barr -- tape #1164, 18 (Box 45)
- UNITE-Boston -- tape #1167, 19 (Box 45)
- Breaking the Silence -- tape #1153, 20 (Box 45)
- Sweatshops-Ch.9 -- tape 1130, 21 (Box 45)
- GUESS Coverage -- tape #1150, 22 (Box 45)
- Robinson's May -- tape #1160, 23 (Box 45)
- Protest At Lazarus -- tape #1165, 24 (Box 45)
- Daybreak -- tape #1162, 25 (Box 45)
- Providence -- tape #1161, 26 (Box 45)
- Hecht's Protest -- tape #1159, 27 (Box 45)
- Protest of Lord Taylor, 28 (Box 45)
- L.A. Sweatshops -- tape #1022, 1 (Box 46)
- Working in the USA -- tape #1019, 2 (Box 46)
- Stop Sweat Shops -- tape #992, 3 (Box 46)
- More Working History, 4 (Box 46)
- Workplace Beat: Covering the Bottom Line, 5 (Box 46)
- Southern Exposure, 6 (Box 46)
- MLK Day-Lichtenburg -- tape #1018, 7 (Box 46)
- State of the Unions / a presentation of California Working Group, 8 (Box 46)
- ACTWU Press Conference -- tape #949, 9 (Box 46)
- Agreement Address -- tape #979, 10 (Box 46)
- Katie Quan -- tape #1020, 11 (Box 46)
- Exec Comp Soundbites -- tape #948, 12 (Box 46)
- Prison Labor/Prison Blues, 13 (Box 46)
- Recording the American Experience, 14 (Box 46)
- ACTWU in Action -- tape #957, 15 (Box 46)
- Charles Kernaghan -- tape #964, 16 (Box 46)
- California Working Group -- tape #961, 17 (Box 46)
- Dept. of Labor-Hall of Fame -- tape #973, 18 (Box 46)
- Made in the USA -- tape #959, 19 (Box 46)
- Horn/Eisenberg -- Crafted with Pride, 20 (Box 46)
- From the Killing Fields -- tape #967, 21 (Box 46)
- With One Voice -- tape #716, 1 (Box 47)
- Susan Cowell -- tape #681, 2 (Box 47)
- One Day Longer: The Story of the Frontier Strike -- tape #1242, 3 (Box 47)
- Cesar Chavez With Rain Fair -- tape #703, 4 (Box 47)
- Restoring Employee Rights is Good for America, 5 (Box 47)
- We Do the Work -- tape #719, 6 (Box 47)
- El Fieston ILGWU Spot -- tape #718, 7 (Box 47)
- 1989 AFL-CIO Convention - tape #680, 8 (Box 47)
- The True Cost of NAFTA -- tape #722, 9 (Box 47)
- GUESS Rage Against the Machine, LA, CA; Channel 20, MTV 12/15/1997 -- tape #1209, 10 (Box 47)
- Monterey Mills - Internal Organizing / Strike Campaign Local 777, Central Dist., J.B., Midwest Regional Joint Board -- tape #1203, 1990; 11 (Box 47)
  Dec. 1987-April 1990 -- MASTER
- The Spirit of '43: the Coming of Age of Labor in Vermont -- tape #1202, 12 (Box 47)
- UNITE!: A Message from president Bruce Raynor -- 12/06/2001, 13 (Box 47)
- UNITE for the Future -- Convention 6/1999, Miami Beach -- tape #1241, 14 (Box 47)
- Bessie Cohen - World Today, CNN, Feb. 24, 1999 -- tape #1240, 15 (Box 47)
- AFL-CIO TWUA Petition -- tape #1211, 16 (Box 47)
- A Message From President Bruce Raynor -- November 2001, 17 (Box 47)
  English
- First Tuesday - Sweetening the Medicine -- Nov.. 1990 -- tape #1204, 18 (Box 47)
- Friend of the DOL, Sidney Hillman -- 10/1/1993, 19 (Box 47)
- UNITE Protests in Philadelphia --tape #1214, 20 (Box 47)
- UNITE Protests -- tape #1213, 1997; 21 (Box 47)
- UNITE!: A Message from President Bruce Raynor -- tape #1245, 2001; 22 (Box 47)
- UNITE/Living Wage -- tape #1243, 23 (Box 47)
- The People vs. Farah, 1 (Box 48)
- Life and Times (Wednesday Edition) #8035 -- tape #1198, 2 (Box 48)
- Hard Copy three-part series on Nicaraguan sweatshops - November 1997 -- tape #1199, 3 (Box 48)
- People Get Ready: UNITE Southern Region 1997 -- tape #1197, 4 (Box 48)
- Common Sense Economics: the Economy is not like the Weather -- tape #1201, 5 (Box 48)
- Cavanaugh's Corner; GUESS what? -- 12/6/1997 -- tape #1212, 6 (Box 48)
- UNITED Protests -- 10/4/1997 -- tape #1215, 7 (Box 48)
- GUESS Outlet Protests -- Dec. 4, 1997 -- tape #1210, 8 (Box 48)
- UNITE Protest -- Dec. 5, 1997 -- tape #1205, 9 (Box 48)
- UNITE/Sweatshops -- Dec. 5, 1997 -- tape #1206, 10 (Box 48)
- UNITE/Sweatshops -- Dec. 6, 1997 -- tape #1207, 11 (Box 48)
- UNITE #6 -- 6/29/1995, 12 (Box 48)
- UNITE - Day 2 - #2 -- 6/30/1995, 13 (Box 48)
- ACTWU #2 -- 6/28/1995, 14 (Box 48)
- ILGWU -- Day 4 - #19 -- 6/27/1995, 15 (Box 48)
- ILGWU -- Day 4 -- #17 -- 6/27/1995, 16 (Box 48)
- ILGWU -- Day 4 -- #16 -- 6/27/1995, 17 (Box 48)
- Segment on DC Labor Rally -- 8/31/1991, 1 (Box 49)
- Jesse Jackson - ACTWU Convention - 1990, 2 (Box 49)
- UNITE, 3 (Box 49)
- ILGWU - #2, 4 (Box 49)
- ILGWU - Day 2 - #5 -- 6/24/1995, 5 (Box 49)
- ILGW - Day 3 - tape 7 - 6/26/1995, 6 (Box 49)
- UNITE - 6/30/1995 - Day 2 - #1, 7 (Box 49)
- ACTWU - #4 - 6/28/1995, 8 (Box 49)
- UNITE Convention Program 1995, 9 (Box 49)
- Mario Cuomo Addresses ACTWU 1990 Convention, 10 (Box 49)
- Jack Sheinkman - Keynote Address - ACTWU 1990 Convention, 11 (Box 49)
- ACTWU 1993 Convention - Jesse Jackson, 12 (Box 49)
- ACTWU Convention Video - 1993, 13 (Box 49)
- ACTWU/Jack Sheinkman Convention Program, 14 (Box 49)
- ACTWU - tape #1 -- 6/28/1995, 1 (Box 50)
- UNITE #5 -- 6/29/1995, 2 (Box 50)
- ILGWU Day 3 -- #11 -- 6/26/1995, 3 (Box 50)
- ILGWU Day 4 -- 6/27/1995, 4 (Box 50)
- ACTWU #6 -- 6/28/1995, 5 (Box 50)
- ACTWU #2 -- 6/28/1995, 6 (Box 50)
- ACTWU #3 -- 6/28/1995, 7 (Box 50)
- ILGWU Day 3 -- #9 -- 6/26/1995, 8 (Box 50)
- Tape #2; 4/22/1969 -- PR Back Home, 9 (Box 50)
- Isabella Harlow & Emma Starn, 10 (Box 50)
- Balelaya TV, 11 (Box 50)
  spelling questionable - handwriting is hard to read
- TWUA COPE -, 12 (Box 50)
- Unlabeled, 13 (Box 50)
- Safety Council - Rabbi Bernstein, 14 (Box 50)
- ACWA - Chambersberg, PA -- April 14, 1956, 15 (Box 50)
- Walter P. Reuther, 16 (Box 50)
- Harry Frumenman, 17 (Box 50)
- Depressed Arcas #2, 18 (Box 50)
- Meeting Stanley Girl (actress) and 2 Genuine Union girls -- 2/13/1956, 19 (Box 50)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Program #9, 20 (Box 50)
- Unlabeled, 21 (Box 50)
- Unlabeled, 22 (Box 50)
- unlabeled, 23 (Box 50)
  1 box, 8 floppies
- Oneita Strike - Contract Meeting #2, 24 (Box 50)
- 3 unlabeled open reels, 25 (Box 50)
- ITWUA, 26 (Box 50)
- 1992 ILGWU Convention: 6/19/1992; Hillary Clinton Speaks to 1992 delegates' (Box 51)
  - 1992 ILGWU Convention: 6/19/1992; Hillary Clinton Speaks to 1992 delegates, 1 (Box 51)
- 1992 ILGWU Convention: 6/19/1992; Hillary Clinton Speaks to 1992 delegates (Box 52)
  - 1992 ILGWU Convention: 6/19/1992; Hillary Clinton speaks to 1992 delegates, 1 (Box 52)
- 1995 ILGWU Convention' (Box 53)
  - 1995 ILGWU Convention, 1 (Box 53)
- ILGWU Day 4-#16; June 27, 1995' (Box 54)
  - ILGWU Day 4 #16; June 16, 1995, 1 (Box 54)
- ILGWU Day 4-#16; June 27, 1995' (Box 55)
  - ILGWU Day 4 #17; June 27, 1995, 1 (Box 55)